[Music]
i never thought that i would find a way
out
i never thought i'd hear my heartbeat so
loud
i can't believe there's something left
in my chest anymore
but goddamn you got me in love again
i used to think that i was made out of
stone
i used to spend so many nights on my own
i never knew i hadn't made the dance
anymore
you got
[Music]
never ever ever met somebody like you
you got me
[Music]
so many nights my tears fell harder than
rain
scared i would take my broken heart to
the grave
i'd rather die than have to live in a
storm like before
but god damn you got me in love again
show me the heavens right here baby
[Music]
you got me
i can't believe i can't believe i
finally found someone
[Music]
i can't believe there's something left
in my chest anymore
you got me
[Music]
you
[Applause]
[Music]
you got me
again
[Music]
[Applause]
you